A Guide to the John Wells research notes, 1871-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Architect lists and card files, n.d., Extent: 18 boxes. (Box 1-15c)
  - Stinson, D.H. (Mississippi) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Terry, _ (Mississippi) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Tinsley, W.P. (Mississippi) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Abrahams, Theodore (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Abrams, A.P. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Aiken, William Martin (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Anderson, D.J. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Andrews, Robert Day (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Ashbury, Louis H. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Attaway, Drew H. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Ayers, Henry (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Baker, Leander (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Baldwin, James J. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Barbot & Seyle (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Barnwell, John G. and Bayard L. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Bealer, William P. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Bellonby, L.A. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Beacham & LeGrand (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Beebe, Harwood (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Beers & Farley (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Benson & Barbot (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Berg, Gustavus Theodore (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Berryman, George R. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Betelle, James O. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Bettsworth, W.W. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Biggers, James W. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Birch, Mahlon Thomas (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Black, A.W. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Black, Edgar Otho (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Black, Fingal C. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Black, H.C. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Blair, Alexander (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Bleckley, Haralson (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Bonfoey, F.L. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Bonitz, H.E. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Bossom, Alfred C. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Bradford, Jules L. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Breeding, Harry D. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Brendon, Charles (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Bridges, James D. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Brite, James (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Bleckley, Haralson (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Brown, A. Ten Eyck (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Brown, A.W. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Brown, Robert (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Bullard & Son (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Burgess, W.C. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Burnham & Bliesner (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Burrell, Seymour (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Cain, John Jefferson (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Carlisle, Aiken (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Carson, John (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Carter, Avery (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Carter, T.T. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Casey, Joseph Huntley (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Cathcart, Samuel M. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Chapman, Hugh R. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Chase, William J.J. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Choate, Charles E. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Chunn, C.H. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Clark, Lloyd A. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Collins, J. Frank (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Comes, John T. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Constantine, Augustus (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Cooke, William W. (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Corse, Henry (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Cosby, Dabney (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Cothran & Cothran (South Carolina) (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Cramer, Eugene (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Critchton & Harrison (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cunningham, F.H. & J.G. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Cusachs, Philip Alain (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Dallis, Park A. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Daly, John D. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Davis, Brinton B. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Davis C.C. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Deal, Fred R. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Delano and Aldrich (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Dennis, Fred (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Denny, Willis F. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Devereux, John Henry (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Devereux, Leslie W. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Dingle, J.B. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Dinkelburg, Frederick Philip (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Donaldson & Meier (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Douden, William (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Downing, W.T. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Draper, Earle Sumner (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Drummond, E. Lynn (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Dunne, E.J. & W.K. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Durang, Francis Ferdinand (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Edens, Allen W. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Eichberg, Alfred (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Eisenschmidt, Robert (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Ellington, Page (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Epton, Leland P. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Etter, William (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Evans, Alfred F. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Fant, Charles W. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Faris, F.F. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Flagg, Ernest (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Foggett, A.W. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Foggette, E. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Fogarty, James (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Freeman, George A., Jr. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Freund, John, Jr. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Fuller, Rex G. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Gaines, Henry I. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Gaisford, John (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Gebhardt, A. Paul (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Gilbert, Bradford L. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Gilchrist, Alfred D. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Golucke, James W. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Goodrich, Lewis F. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Greene, J. Perry (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Green, James M. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Greene, James E. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Griffin, A.M. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Hamby & Hamby (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Hampton, Martin Luther (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Harper, W.D. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Harrall, Henry D. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Hartman, Charles C. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Hastings, Thomas (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Hawes, Edward, Jr. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Hazard, F. Arthur (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Heaton, Roy K. & Company (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Hemphill, James Calvin (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Hewetson, Ralph, E.B. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Hibbs, Henry C. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Hicks, Leon McDuff (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Hoffman, F. Burrall (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Holler, A.D. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Holman, Arthur E. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Holmes, Rutledge (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Holmes & Von Schmid (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Hook, Charles C. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Hopkins, Alfred H. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Hoppin & Koen (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Hornblower & Marshall (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Howe, W.B.W. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Huddart, John J. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Huggins, William J. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Hunter, James E. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Hunter, Leonard L. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Hyer, David B. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Irvin, Willis (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Harder, Julius (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Ittner, William Butts (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Johannsen, Heinrich H. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Johnson, James Herbert (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Johnson, J. Carroll (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Johnson, J.H. (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Jones, Edward C. & Francis D. Lee (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Jones, H. Olin (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Kaufmann, Otto (South Carolina) (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Kay, John A. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Keating, Thomas (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Kebbon, Eric (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Keeble, Edwin A. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Keeley, P.C. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Keith Company, Architects (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Kilham & Hopkins (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Ladshaw & Ladshaw (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - LaFaye, George E. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Koeith, Lawrence A.H. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Laird, John (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Lamble, Henry S. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - LaMotte, A. Gamewell (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Lauritzen, Peter J. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Lawrence, J.R. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Lawrence, Joseph T. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Lax, Joe Murry (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Layton, Soloman Andrew (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Lee, Rudolph E. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Leitner, Joseph F. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Leo, Gustave E. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Letellier, Louis S. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Lide, C.M. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Linthicum, Hill C. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Livingston, W.T. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Lowery, Samuel F. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Ludlow & Peabody (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Lynch, L.E.C. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Macmurphy & Story (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Mahoney, George F. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Marsh, Marion R. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Martin, Haskell Hair (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Marye, Philip Thornton (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Maynard, R.W. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - McClare, C.H. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - McCollough, E.H. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - McCrady Brothers & Cheves (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - McCrossin Brothers & Thomas (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - McCullough, J.D. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - McDonald Brothers (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - McElfatrick, John B. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - McGee, Hubert T. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - McGhee & McGhee (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - McGoodwin & Hawley (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - McGrath, Robert N. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - McInerny, Michael (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - McMichael, James M. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - McMillan, Charles (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Mebane, C.A. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Medary, Milton B. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Melton, Allen L. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Merry, A. Brian (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Miller, Robert (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Mills, Robert (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Mims, _ (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Mitcham, R.W. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Mowbray & Uffinger (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Mullet, Alfred B. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Mullinax, R.D. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Murphy, E.A. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Nash, Paul H. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Neilson, John Crawford (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Nelson, Walter R. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Neves, William D. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Newcomer, John D. (South Carolina) (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Niernsee, John R. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Nimitz, Arthur Edward (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Norman, G.L. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - O'Connor, James W. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Okel & Cooper (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Oliver, Henry (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Orr, Fred J. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Osborne, Adlai (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Ott, Siberia (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Otto, Olaf (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Owens, J.L. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Parker, Charles Edward (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Parkins, W.H. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Parsons, E.M. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Pauly Jail Building & Manufacturing Company (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Peabody, Julian (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Peeps, William H. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Pelz, Paul J. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Perkins, F.E. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Perkins, George Bacheler (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Pinckney, Thomas M. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Pittman, S.L. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Poley, G.M. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Porter, A. H. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Preacher, G. Lloyd (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Pringle, Robert Smith (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Proffitt, Luther D.(South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Rankin, Kellogg & Crane (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Rayfield, W.A. & Company (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Reid, Thomas G. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Rice, John Henry, III (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Richards, Ernest Vincent (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Ritcher, Abner A. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Robert & Company (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Rogers, Fred G. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Rogers, James Gamble (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Rogers, Willard G. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Rorke, Edwin G. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Rosenwald Fund (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Russell, William P. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Rutledge, E.B. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Salter, James A. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Sams, J.H. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Sawyer, Frank McMaster (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Scroggs & Ewing (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Shand, Gadsden E. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Shaw, Fred Gordon (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Short, R. Thomas (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Sibbert, Edward F. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Silber, Norman (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Simmons, William Walter (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Simons & Lapham (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Simons, S. Lewis (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Simpson, Joseph B. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Smith, B.F.(South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Smith, Elroy G. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Smith, Francis P. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Smith, Frederick J. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Smith, George G. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Smith, Jesse M. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Smith, Walter H. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Smith, William W. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Snook, John B. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Snyder, Jacob (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Sompayrac, Edwin Douglas (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Stafford & Quinn (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Standard Oil Company of New Jersey (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Starr, Julian S. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Stevenson & Green (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Stewart, George Wilson (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Stone, Joseph (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Sumner, Ernest (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Swan, Charles D. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Sweeney, F.R. (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Tatum, Harold (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Thomas, Martin & Kirkpatrick (South Carolina) (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Thompson & Frohling (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Tilden, George T. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Tilton, Edward L. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Tinsley, S.P. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Tippett, Robert L. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Todd, A.W. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Tomlinson, William Sidney, Sr. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Trowbridge, S.D. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Tufts, R.B. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Turner, Mark Toney (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Underwood, H.A. and Company (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Upjohn, Hobart B. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Urquhart, James B. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Vance, S.N. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Vatet, Oscar V. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Walker, George E. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Walker, Henry F. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Walker, Lewis J. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Walker, Nat Gaillard (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Wallin, Henrik (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Walter, Frank C. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Waring, George W. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Ward, William R. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Wayne, Daniel G. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Wells, Osborne (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Wendell, Henry T.E. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Wessinger & Stork (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Whaley, Christopher L. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Whaley, W.B. Smith (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Wheaton, Francis B. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Wheeler, O.D. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - White, Columbus (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - White, Edward B. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - White, Edwin (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - White, Hugh E. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Whittaker, Miller F. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Wilkins, W.J. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Williams, W. Paul (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Wilson, J.A. & W.T. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Wilson, Charles Coker (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Windham, W.P. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Windrim, James H. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Witcover, Hyman W. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Youmans, Paul H. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Zeigler, Daniel G. (South Carolina) (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Adams, George Q. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Adams, James (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Adams, John Wesley (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Adams, Walter S. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Adams, William A. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Adsit, Cyrus Boyd (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Agee, Polk W. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Ahlschlager, Walter W. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Aiken, William Martin (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Albertson, Benjamin N. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Alexander, Archibald (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Alford, Eugene C. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Alford, Roy (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Alger, Richard W. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Alsop, M.M. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Alston, Philip (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Alsup, Beauregard C. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Alsup, Jefferson D. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Alsup, Joseph C. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Alverson, S.A. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Alves, Bernard S. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Andrews, W.J. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Archer, John (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Arnold, Reginald V. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Ash, Ed (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Asmus, Christian A. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Atkinson, Carl W. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Ault, Conrad (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Aultman, F.C. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Ausfield, Frederick (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Awsumb, George (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Awsumb, George W. & Son (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Awsumg, Wells (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Aydelott, Alf L. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Badger, _ (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Bailey, Walter T. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Baker, James (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Baldwin, Mathias Harvey (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Barber, Charles I. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Barksdale, Wilton C. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Barge, Waggoner, Sumner & Cannon (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Barnes, H.G. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Barnwell, Bayard L. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Barnwell, John G. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Bartlett, Buddemeyer & Chamberlain (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Bates, William (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Baumann, Albert B. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Baumann, J.F. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Beale, G.S. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Bearden, Charles E. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Beaver, Leon (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Beeson, D.R. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Behles, E.P. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Bell, George H. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Bell, J.E. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Bell, Mifflin E. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Bell, W.M. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Bell, W.R., Jr. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Benjamin, A.T. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Bentley, C.J. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Benton, E. Spencer (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Berlin & Swern (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Bianculli, Mario (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Biggers, T.J. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Billis, O.J. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Billis, William J. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Birchful, J.R. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Bishop, George, Jr. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Blatherwick, W.F. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Bleakley, Charles (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Blount, _ (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Bobo, _ (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Bogle, _ (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Bond, M. James (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Boone, W.B. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Brackney, C.C. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Briggs, Asa (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Briggs, O.J. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Broadwell, James J. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Brown, Thomas (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 80)